WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Sasuke...?
No... Who is he?
He's got the same Sharingan
as Sasuke.
Really...
who'd believe a kid like you to
have the Nine-Tailed Fox in him.
Why does that guy know
about the Nine-Tailed Fox?!
Naruto-kun, you will come with us.
Growl
Chidori
Roar Sasuke!
That guy is... close by!
That guy!
Nii-san...
Today...
when school's over,
help me train for a Shuriken Jutsu...
I'm busy... Have father teach you.
But you're better at Shuriken Jutsu,
nii-san...
Even I can see that.
You always treat me
like a pest, nii-san.
Ouch!
Forgive me Sasuke...
Some other time, okay?
I don't have time to
pay attention to you today.
You're always jabbing my forehead
and saying "Forgive me, Sasuke."
You also say "not today,"
but there's never a day.
Father.
Huh?
Why doesn't nii-san
pay any attention to me?
That guy's a little strange...
He's the type that doesn't really like
to become intimate with people.
Why?
I don't know.
I am his father and
still I can't read that boy...
Here!
Your boxed lunch, Sasuke!
If you're worried about doing
Shuriken Jutsu practice,
I will watch you when you get home.
They're not practices,
they're training!
See you later!
Sasuke-chan, are you on
your way to school?
Yes.
I saw Itachi-chan earlier on.
He's really become a man.
He's already a top-notch Shinobi.
He graduated at the head of his class
at the Academy at the age of seven,
and attained Chunin level
at the age of ten, didn't he?
He became adept at using
Sharingan at the age of eight.
Yes, I remember.
That boy is truly
the pride of the Uchiha clan.
By the way,
how old are you now, Sasuke-chan?
I'm the same age as
when nii-san graduated,
but I can't...
What's the matter?
Hey!
Stop talking nonsense!
Oh my, dear.
Sasuke, both you and Itachi
come from the same Uchiha clan,
the pedigree of
the Hidden Leaf Village.
Have confidence!
You'll be an amazing
Shinobi just like Itachi one day.
Yeah!
See you later!
Do your best!
Study hard!
That's right...
I come from the same Uchiha clan
as nii-san...
I won't lose to nii-san!
I'm pretty late...
What was that?
I had the feeling
there was someone there...
The lights are out.
Even though it's not time for bed...
What's this?!
W-What's this?!
What in the world is this?!
Uncle... Aunt...
Father... Mother...!
Father? Mother?
Aren't you here?
There's somebody here!
Move!
Father! Mother!
Nii-san!
Father and Mother are...!
Why? For what reason?!
Who in the world would do
something like this...?
Nii-san... What are you...?
What are you doing,
nii-san!
Foolish younger brother...
Mangekyo Sharingan!
My legs...!
Stop!
Nii-san!
Don't make me see this!
Why...?
Why did you, nii-san...?!
No...!
No...
Aunt! Uncle!
Father! Mother!
Stop it! Nii-san!
Don't kill Father and Mother!
W-Why...
Why did you...? Nii-san...?
To measure my abilities...
Measure your abilities...?
Just for that?
Are you saying that...
Just for that...
you killed them all?
That is of great importance.
What do you mean...?
Don't talk rubbish!
I'm scared...
I'm scared!
Don't kill me...!
D-Don't kill me!
You are not even worth killing...
Foolish younger brother...
If you want to kill me, begrudge me!
Hate me!
And keep on surviving in
that unsightly manner...
Just continue fleeing and fleeing
and hang onto your life!
Shall we go outside...?
These guys aren't just anybody...
Itachi-san, it'll be a pain in the neck
if this kid moves around and...
Maybe I better chop off
a leg just in case...
W-What did he say?!
Now then...
Long time no see...
Sasuke.
Uchiha Itachi!
Uchiha... Itachi?
The same as Sasuke...
An Uchiha...
Huh... Sharingan...
And moreover,
he resembles you a lot...
Who the hell is he?
He's my younger brother.
But I heard that the entire Uchiha clan
had been murdered.
By you.
Uchiha Itachi... I will kill you!
I must kill one certain man
without fail!
That man...
My brother...
I thought I couldn't die...
without killing him, but...
That's the guy that Sasuke
was saying...
The man he wanted to kill...
It's just as you said...
I held a grudge against you
and hated you.
For the singular purpose of
killing you, I...
I...
have lived my life!
Sasuke...!
Chidori...?
I will kill you!
Die!
W-What's going on?!
I can't believe that Sasuke's Jutsu
was so easily thwarted...
This doesn't look good!
I've got to do something!
Chakra permeates the air...
I see...
So this is the Nine-Tailed Fox Chakra!
You jerk!
You're in the way!
Sasuke!
Damn it!
Ninja Art: Summo...
You're too slow!
Huh...? I can't feel the Chakra...
Damn! Damn! Why is it?!
My sword Shark Skin
has the ability to...
cut through and eat Chakra!
It's a pain in the neck
if the kid moves around
and uses Jutsu like that...
Before these legs...
Should I chop off these arms?
Why doesn't it emerge?!
It's pointless...
What?
You guys just don't know me much,
do you?
This man Jiraiya does not fall victim
to any woman's allurement,
but rather his forte is
winning women's affection!
I'm not made to blindly follow after
a woman's feminine charm!
When you get to my level,
women yelp with delight
at my sex appeal!
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
Watch out, Sasuke!
Naruto, don't help him.
But... Sasuke is!
It is your duty to watch
through this battle, Naruto.
What?!
This is his fight...
This represents everything that
he has been carrying up to now.
Next time:
"Foolish Younger Brother. Hate, Detest!"